From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack, you smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, truce
Dropping spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping Lenore's on guard tricks bringing love Lola Rudy Marbles fan from above
Like the away can step in the flame. We call your truth. We say your name. It's wow
That's real. It's so deep play now grab your tea and slay the dead like the away kids
Don't look away your shadows talking it came to stay we laugh we cry we speak we scream live from the madness
This ain't no dream
Go ahead, Tricks.
Excuse you.
Hi, guys.
How are you?
Happy August 1st.
Today is August 1st.
It's August, September, October, November, December.
We have five months left of the year.
Good morning.
I thought I'd do a little wake and bake.
Longer collected read today. I had a good time last night on tiktok. I'm almost at 700 subscribers
It's just been a couple weeks there
So it's going really fast, you know, it's like we'll have larger numbers, you know, but uh
Okay
Cars organize a little bit
and it's just popped out.
So you got King of Swords.
This is your energy.
King of Swords is like done with such.
He doesn't take any crap from anybody.
He's a very good communicator.
Could be a Gemini Libra and an Aquarius, right?
They're same.
Hello, hello Shepard, how are you?
Oh, sweet God, oh, King of Cubs.
We got two kings coming out in a row.
Kind of mastering your mind and mastering your emotions, okay.
Coming into the Emperor energy.
Also, something is hidden right here.
Something's being hidden.
Yeah, I'm having the whole, see, talk over there.
I started after the show last night.
It was fun.
I just did, I went through the whole deck.
and just answer questions and
What really well I got a bunch of new subscribers. I got some, you know
little gifts and stuff
roses
Okay, these are looking good. Okay
Well, so we got
Page of Cups is the page of cups and little fish in the little fish in the cup. There's nothing a little fishy about the page of cups sometimes
Sometimes it's an offer but the name of this deck. This is just the gold foil rider weight called the gold foil tarot
I will put this up. I will do a review of this deck and put the link in I have an Amazon influencer store now
But this was a gift from Amanda Erickson
These were on my Amazon wishlist and they are great great cards
Okay, Ace of Wands, something being handed to you
that's gonna make you really passionate and exciting.
Are TikTok viewers better in 60 or two?
No, I mean, it's like TikTok viewers are,
they come in real quick.
They, most of the time they just like, you know,
pass by the live, you know.
But a lot of people do stay, they ask a question.
And I just do fast paced readings there, okay?
Yes, we got four. Oh, you got ten of swords, but it's in reverse. It's coming out of some kind of heartbreaker betrayal. I
Know that who you feel sometimes someone doesn't tell with that, but this is the ten of swords in reverse
It's one of the few reversals in the in this deck that I have right now, right? And so
That's it there's a card to be reversed that is the card it's the swords falling out of the back
else we got
The devil is a devil card. We have the devil card
You know, this can sometimes be in your lower self, sometimes there's bad contracts, sometimes there's addiction, sometimes there's
toxic relationships.
But you know, the other side of the coin is the lovers with this double card.
And so it can actually be raised into something beautiful if the lower side can be recognized.
You like it later in the background?
Thank you.
And the fool, new journey.
Maybe after that, after that double car
is time for like a new cycle to begin
and the return of innocence.
I think the devils are the fools,
the very innocent cars, especially after that double car.
Okay.
Thank you, he-man, thank you, he-man.
Yeah, we have like a little thing set up over here.
It's pretty cool.
Here we go.
Let's see the lights, how am I working right there?
Pretty cool.
I have a little audience at all times.
Yeah, so how was the last night?
Like, you know, I had Taco Bell like last night.
I had a little bit of ingestion.
Like, you know, throughout like a little acid reflux.
So I kind of like woke up a few times during the night,
but I had some good dreams.
I had some kind of 90 day fiance show in the background and so I was dreaming about that
Anybody remember 90 day fiance?
One of my favorite shows
Yeah, pretty cool
What else do we got?
Okay, Japanicles. This is somebody coming
Maybe a younger person coming with like hey, I have an idea
I have here like I have this project or something that you can help with but they're bringing you something
And then you can help make it grow.
So I don't know if it's kind of money or projects.
What's the, what does it have to do with?
It has to do with a tower.
Towers are these shocking moments of our life
that something unexpected may happen,
shake things up a little bit, but towers are all bad.
Sometimes things need to be shaken up, right?
I'm gonna put these in there.
This is the way that was a little collective reading. I'm happy to do a
Reading for anybody that would like one how many cigarettes so I have three cigarettes left, but I have like you know many butts
Oh
Finish my alcohol less than two and a half years. I just had a couple coffees
Right to bed. You get the cats right here behind me, too. Let's do the cats
Hi guys
That's my mother and son Lola's the mom and the tricks little boy. Hey come on over come on over. Hi
Himsles you give me kisses
Trixie oh
Pardon me
Sorry
Yeah, so it's been going pretty good on this show, too, you know, I'm having a really good month in the show
Of course, guys, they're really amazing.
Contributors this month, I just want to say thank you again,
especially to Ghost.
I want to say thank you to Random Guy as well.
And I know other people, a lot of other people
have gotten memberships, donated memberships.
Thank you, Christine.
Thank you, Summer.
Thank you, School of Athens.
Thank you, everybody.
That is,
The donate I hope you dig it guys do like the the emojis that are available to the members you can see
Sam and is a member and
He's using the some of the emojis. They're pretty cool. I
Think I chose some good ones some unique ones that are not on YouTube and so
I'm a hopefully like that. Good morning guys
So I was saying man opposed to the link. Okay. Well, let's see who comes on today. We'll have a free morning
We'll have an open panel morning
Maybe we'll do
Sponsor panel later tonight, but come on up guys. Oh, sorry
Fixed you're showing your balls
Don't show those don't show this okay
Okay, the chat's a little bit shocked the chat's a little bit shocked today
Okay, come on up sick. We'll see hi
Say how things go. Hi, baby. Oh
Hi, babe
Like that. Hi
Yeah, so some people are a fan of the I do is I've been doing it so AI videos and music some people like it some people don't
Open payout love open payout this morning. Hi, I beat a
Good morning. I just woke up. Here's mr. Trixie. Hi. Hi
You be cuddly today. Yeah, we got open panel today
I'll open it up for whoever wants to come up. I think sick
Hi
Fixed is that well him and marbles are the ones that aren't fixed
Wars over all yeah, hey Trevor
How are you guys doing today?
Yeah, so on the on tiktok. I have about 700 subscribers now
Where's Lenora? Yeah, Lenora has been like, well, here's Lola right here. Lenora likes to spend time outside
She's I saw her like a neighbor's backyard like stunning. There's Lola right there. Oh
You're yawning. I
Don't know Lenora. I wish she would come inside more. She comes in a few times a day. I don't know
she's like
Spook to something in the house or the other cats are bothering her or something like that, but she like
She's been outside a lot. The thing is just because of the nice weather
Thank you. Thank you yesterday. Yeah, and
It was cool seeing some people
In my TikTok yesterday after this show I did go over there
Had had a good reading
You know, I have on this on the screen it says like, you know ask your question people will just come in to ask their question
It was really busy yesterday. Just like you know one after the other always people in the room. So I
Got my cash up
Up there too, I look forward to maybe booking some readings through there
Yeah, hey Lola. Hi, babe
Yeah, I think 30 a.m
You got a kitty. Oh cool. Oh, maybe that will like, you know prove his mood. I think a kitty cat is always good, too
It's good for the mood. Hi Lola. Oh yawning over there. You're on it
Yeah, I'm smoking cigarettes today
Because they don't sell my
Cigars anymore, but I've almost gone through a whole pack in like a whole hours
They're a little bit lighter though than the cigars. I've been smoking my smoky swishers for months and they
Would have you waking up?
Hopping also do all my laundry. I'm sorting so many things out. The house is pretty clean
You can see it's relatively it's a little bit messy, you know, but uh
There's my light show right there. It's pretty cool
I found your cat sir
So thank you guys for being here this morning.
I hope everyone's good.
I'll pin the link if I can.
Everyone's welcome on up.
Have a nice day.
Good chat, let's see.
There we go.
Hi.
Okay.
Yeah, so I've been missing this like new season of...
of a 90-day fiance, has anybody been watching it?
Okay, let me see if I got this, there we go.
You can pin the link.
There we go.
It's a pin, 22 people in chat.
Hey, Trix, I got my,
my stand set up a little bit.
Hi.
Okay, there he goes.
Good morning everybody. Thank you. Yeah, it's like the light looks really good. I love that light right there
This I'm gonna
Look into the more lighting. This is from Timu. I got also like a vacuum cleaner from Timu
I have like much a few more decks coming on
You know today
Well, I don't know if they'll be here today, but they're gonna be here soon including the cat full of spiders deck by Christina Ricci
I don't know if it'll be the original deck or knockoff, but I do look forward to that one
Hmm
I'll show you
Over here is my my leg. I have a lucky cat here. You can see the lucky cat
There and there's like a monkey. I'm thinking see it there. I see
There's my
See you got it all clean
This table is kind of messy. There's my kitchen. There's got tables full of cards
cat stuff
Let's get a few cat towers
Hopefully you guys are good today
Come on up free panel
Yeah, I had some like three Taco Bell tacos last night and they kind of got
You waking up a little bit
Throughout the night Lula suggestion. Hello the boss. How are you? How's everybody?
But it is nice being a clean clean clean house, right?
Got some other stuff to
Hey, hey, hey Lola or Lola I come over here Lola come on
Lola come on
Remember when Lola was pregnant last year? Hi. Hi. Hi, and she gave birth under the TV set
Mm-hmm, and I remember you and magic because it had two little black cats
Yeah, unfortunately I
Haven't seen any of the I haven't seen Freya. I haven't seen I
Haven't seen
Tux or pie. I haven't seen pie in a long time. I have a cat named pie. I haven't seen him for a while
They kind of just get integrated in the neighborhood. I just hope that you know, they're okay out there and
There are coyotes and stuff her name was Lola. She was a showgirl. Hi
Do you ever see that this painting? I'll show you this. I found this when I was walking one day and it kind of reminds me of me
But maybe it doesn't look like me. I don't know you can have your own thoughts about it, but here
This is my there's my stairs. Hold on. It's my stairs
stairs, but
This I found one day
Kind of weird, huh
I thought it kind of looked like me a little bit. I just found it on the street. It's got a big canvas
Someone had not completed it
But kind of looks like me a little bit
Here's my view
You can see oh
Here's my view. There's a little bit great this morning. There's
See Lenore's always in his backyard. Lenore are you there? Hi? Hi. I see you over there. Well
Yeah, little parking lot over there there's a bird over there. Hey, hi. Hi
My little backyard
There you go. Hi
Let's turn on this, okay. Oh
Yeah on a tea talk though, I do like I get a lot of spam though I get a lot of like
Hello, dear. Where are you from? And they just ask me where you from and then they're gonna like give like the oh, well
Would you like to like you know, you know date me I?
Must have hundreds of emails, but then now I'm getting some more private personal emails and I
Do I'm enjoying
Tiktok though. There are some attractive people on that website
You know me it
If really hot guys on on tiktok
So you can kind of scroll through then you can like them and it's like I like seeing like straight guys reactions to like you know
But you guys can come over to tiktok to it's just like
I wanted to, well, and TikTok has different rules, right?
If I was to do this on TikTok,
I would do this is that,
I would immediately would say restricted video
and it does not allow usually any kind of smoke,
even in cigarettes, you can't have cigarettes.
So it's kind of hard to remember to smoke off of camera.
This kick too has different rules.
Like I was on kick and I don't know if like, you know and things are poor and bombed.
I'm just mentioning it because I'm trying to get to a thousand subscribers there
and then I'll be monetized like almost fully. Then when I get 10,000 I'll be really monetized there.
That'd be pretty cool. I got 10,000 subscribers on TikTok.
I just see like a lot of people, how much were the headphones?
I think these were like 30 or 40 bucks, these ones?
Yeah, maybe they're like 40 bucks.
I'm gonna be looking into some new,
actually I have a microphone, professional microphone
that I can use once I get a computer.
And so, I just need a little advice on
which will have a port for
My VR
Because there's these mini computers now. There's a few hundred bucks. I
Think it's probably strong and more powerful than the computer. I have now and they're really small
And I just need to make sure that I get one that I could do VR on so I do have a VR headset
Hopefully it won't be more than a couple hundred bucks
so I
Have everything else I need have all the I
See the computer part
So how are we doing guys 27 people in chat? Good morning
Yeah, I think I will I actually applied for the influencer program on Amazon and I got accepted into it
so I'll probably put a lot of
things I've ordered on Amazon some books and some decks and some
equipment and stuff and
I'll review it and then I'll be able to put it on my
Yeah, there isn't up on YouTube I
Do yeah, YouTube is it's working really really well
I just don't want to like just be too overexposed on it like I have been on here every day
I'm still been on every day. I've just shortened up the show because I was doing like 10 hour shows a day sometimes and
You know sometimes, you know, I could be neglectful of other stuff so
but
Yeah, building the brand
I'll have people been talking about the merchant you have some purse available. They're like, hey, there's a $40 Lenore sweatshirt
I think it's a fucking cool sweatshirt though. I'm gonna be ordering samples of them
and
Modeling it
So I look forward to
Showing you that soon. It is Friday August 1st
Let me see. I do have it nice
Yeah, I'm trying to do all the go through all the right steps, right?
So with YouTube I
Was like just started the channel really slowly
Started building up
And I kind of had a plan for it.
Yeah, it's Friday.
Oh gosh, I'm getting a really bad acid reflux
of smoking this vape.
I think the cigarettes are not great either.
It's Friday, hopefully you guys are having a good weekend.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, we'll have a good weekend.
Do you have any, anybody have plans for the weekend?
What's up, FreeSide, how are you?
You have a free piano, so come on up. I will put the banner though for
See
Just a bit of banner up for
There
Click on the join button
It's by the dollar sign if you have a and make sure you are joined because I do have all my
All my content is behind the paywall right now just because
I'd rather just have members have access to it because you know
Might this the lives are for everybody, right? I can have members only lives
But I think I'll just do one of those a week for Q&A maybe an hour just for members
For any thing the members want to say to me and we can have a private members how well like once a week
But and anything else I will usually put after the show
I'll put for members only and so it may look like I have no content, but I have a lot of content
I have actually
Maybe over a thousand hours. I have hundreds of videos
for sure over a thousand hours and so you know I
Do you have to go through like a lot of my older videos that are privatized because there was some porn bombs
I think and I just don't want to
Hopefully uh, you know
There's not like some AI bot that goes through and I'll ever get in trouble for it, but I
Think I've been pretty lucky and I think I've been able to just delete delete most of the
Things but I did notice on StreamYard. It does save the last 50 hours of
of your
shows
And so I can like, you know, like the other day,
I had daddy pigginess on and then we got porn bombed.
I can go back, I can edit out the porn bomb
and then repost that video.
And so I'm gonna try to figure that out today.
Are there's a way to do that?
Hey, Trix.
Hi.
Yeah.
So, thank you, he man. Thank you for your side. I don't know. I guess
Somebody else must have started up or something like that because uh-oh. Yeah, the numbers are falling. I don't know if I'm boring you guys
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
Can you guys hear me? Okay? Maybe the sound is it on? Nope. It was not
Guys hear me better now. I'm so sorry. I forgot to turn my microphone on
Yeah, whoopsie, okay
There's Mr. Tricks. Uh-oh. Scratchin'.
Yeah, we had a good collective reading. I might want to rewind a little, but there was a good collective reading, but I will do another one.
And if anybody would like a reading this morning, I got you. We're free.
Yeah, but so, there are really attractive... Video audio is good, yeah.
There are some very attractive people on TikTok. I don't know if you... I don't know if they actually...
Like these like who you subscribe to and then it will put more but I get a lot of the hot guys
Like I just scroll through and there's a lot of hot guys
And then you can give them like little gifts and they're usually grateful
I think a few people have blocked me because I'm a guy giving them gifts, but most people are like
If not like grateful, they are downright flirtatious back, right?
You saw me twerking at my speedo on TT flirty diamonds
Hold on Florida. Is that the real?
Okay, yeah, that's that for you diamond because you were yeah, you saw me twerking my speo on TT. What is TT?
Oh Tiktok
Yeah, I'm for I did I didn't but I have my speedo like around here somewhere. I think it's like right over
Yeah, I saw it yesterday
Yeah, I had fun with diamond last night. We were on a pebs show
Nice talking to pebs a diamond. Hey, hey, man. Hey guys
We'll have a little bit of heartburn this morning. I can't really move
So did anybody watch 90 day fiance so I watched 90 day fiance from
You know it took me a couple years to find it right once I found it like I wouldn't I wouldn't watch saw the original seasons
I watched them in like a couple days, you know
And then so I've watched every episode almost but I haven't watched this last couple seasons
Because it started getting dumb, you know, it's like shows will kind of jump the shark and it was but it was like a great show
It is like there's this one woman named Danielle and she's kind of like this like
You know this like
Yeah, she lives in a trailer. She's like very
You know kind of cross-eyed and she's red-headed and she has like three teenagers or whatever
And and she went to Tunisia and met this guy Mohammed who's like this much younger
He's in his 20s, and she's in her 50s. I think
And she brings them out and he just disappears once he gets to America, he's out with other women and like very attractive women and blondes, you know, Pamela Anderson types.
And this woman is like sitting at home crying. I mean, it was pretty classic.
You can go look up Danielle and Mohamed.
Pretty funny. Oh, yeah, and then they had this tell-all then like he was saying that she would like
Get on the floor demanding sex and like and then that she smelled like she she she peed on herself
And she had a weird smell in her vagina. I mean, it's like he said that and she starts crying on the show
It's a really funny. You might like that show
Oh, so how are we I came on a little early today because of the 845 I was awake and
Don't know what I'll do today. I'm um, let's see my friend might come over today
but
I don't know he keeps the
Laying delay delaying so
She'll see he hangs out
Hopefully it'll be a fun day. I'm getting I get a little bit
Hired with this weed a little bit
This is a say a really good vape though. This is a a sci-fi barrier or something flavor
Doesn't really taste like it but hey, there's Lola my Lola
You're gonna give me kiss I have a kiss
Hi
You're giving me kisses. Hi
Hi, sweetheart
Lola is such a sweet cat
Yeah, the friend that I have if he's the one that brought me Lola actually did my grinder day ever show up
It wasn't a grinder day and no they never showed up like
But uh, it was my friends supposed to come over but you know, he's like he works on stuff. So
Hi, this is miss Lola. She's a sweetheart
You gonna sit here and guard me. She's a guard. He guards me
But yeah, he brought over Lola one day like in a little in a carrier. He's like I found this cat on the street
She was a kitten, right? You were just a kitten
But uh, and I was like I can't have any more cats. They had like five cats the time
I can't have any more and he's like, oh, well, can I just leave her here for a little bit?
Okay, and so he left her and then I just take had her like see on the couch a little cat carrier for like 10 minutes
And she got her meowing
And I opened it and she had all those boogers in her eye, right?
And I wiped down her eyes and look how beautiful her eyes are.
At least she has a beautiful eye color.
You can see how beautiful, oh yeah, they're green, right?
She has beautiful green eyes.
And so, and she's such a sweet cat.
And so she, and she tricks his mom.
She got, she came and she got knocked up.
You were out, right?
You got pregnant?
But different cats too.
Because one of them was one of the cats that was here, right?
Because one of them looked just like a cat here.
Hi, oh, she's so sweet. She's so sweet and
And then Lenore would always chase her out and so she couldn't like get comfortable
But then finally and when she had to have the kittens
I was so worried that she would have the outside I had to go find them or something like that
outside and like transport them back, but she actually came so she just came back when she was ready to have the kittens and
You had them on Pi day March 14th. They started popping out
and I have one cat out of those cats left out of those five kittens that were
born and I just have tricks the other cats have assimilated into the
neighborhood hopefully they're all alive and happy and healthy but yeah it's a
fun neighborhood for cats to prowl it's just like you know just like pretty
quiet probably
Cat sex everywhere, but really like a lot of animal lovers too though
Like I know that some of my cats like I've come back with collars and air tags and
Looking very fat well cared for so
Cats are all fine
Just kind of let the animals do the animals. Hey bud. Oh, gee. Hey everybody
So guys, but I do recommend joining the membership I have over a hundred members now
But I have everything behind the paywall and so if you do like to like watch old episodes and you don't have a
Membership because a lot were gifted, you know
I want to thank people that gifted memberships and I gifted a bunch like at least probably like maybe 20 this month or something
Yeah
But I'm happy. Oh, also, I don't know. I think that on the first of the month I get to give away some memberships
I'm not sure though. Let me check. I read something about that
membership gifting
Well, you know, it's weird. It's like that. It's like it says we're gonna give away a certain amount of memberships to give away
right
But the ones that they give away whatever that you can give away see
Once you can give away our
Not you don't you don't you don't get monetized with them. Okay, and
Yeah, you can ever have too many cats. So, you know, Lenore
Rudy's where's Rudy Rudy's around here somewhere Rudy's been going outside though. Rudy likes to go outside
Yeah, cats are good energy. Hey, baby. Where they're good energy. See. Oh, oh, this is the college because she comes running. Oh, oh
By my nose biting my nose
Hi
This is a good cat.
Uh-oh, you're biting my nose.
Look, you're on camera.
Yeah.
Hi, babe.
You're on TV?
You're on TV, you know you're famous
You're famous people like to look at Lola
This Lola
Rodimus, you're so rude, but it's so absolutely rude
I'm fatigued because I'm smoking pot and I was going really hard past month
Hi Arthur. Yeah
Look guys, I'll put there, put there.
It's fun to say like that. I'll put the cat. I'll put the cat. Hey, what's up, what's up,
pussycat? What's up pussycat? Hi, good kitty. Hi, hi. Hey, pay your belly, pay your belly.
The knife. Oh, hi. Hey, your belly
Yeah, I give good cat massage I think
You get good cat massage you like oh you like that one of your your neck your neck. Oh
How much weed am I smoking a day?
I miss but this is I've had for like a few days now and look hardly any is I've just been like just
It's so strong. I just like take a like a hit or two and it's like it puts me to sleep
so
I need some more caffeine. Hi babe. Hi
Okay
Hopefully you guys are having a good day. Hopefully
Yeah, but I think I do need some guests like a guest come on up
Or else it's hard to like talk on my own sometimes kind of caffeine vapes. I'll try I
Do you like to have
Well, yeah, it's been 38 minutes, but it's like I do like to have guests on sometimes to talk
I think it may be a little bit early for everybody. So I
understand
Did you feel like coming up link is pinned?
Yeah
We'll see what happens today at least I guess kind of slower day, but maybe we'll pick up hi
Anybody feel like coming on
It's 11 a.m. It feels like boring is a little slow. Yeah
Well
Who else is on right now is anybody else on you can go raid a chat or something that there's somebody else on like
Beta or something speed off
They're a caffeine vape
Let me look let me look to see if anybody's on hold on we're back
Good morning
Morning, so are you gonna start eating healthier cuz I every time I come in the chat someone's like accusing you of looking like you have HIV
Okay, do some exercise
Okay, yep, all right, yep
Don't I look fine? I think I look fine. I look sick. That's what you're saying. What dude you need some fucking
Need to do some exercises change your diet. Yeah, come on man
They're not just saying it for the hell of it. The chat's always right chats always right. It's not they're shortly
I don't have HIV. I don't there's nothing I can do here. All right. See I gotta go. Okay. Well, that was like so rude
I mean, it's like please
You have if you have anything else to do besides accuse me of having M AIDS, you know
I'd like, I'd like to hear it, you know, jeez.
What I put up with.
Anyhow.
So, yeah, that was very rude.
It's a very unbelievable.
Hey, how about we like, we can go say hi to my friend, Danny.
He's showing some funny stuff right now.
This is Danny Stranger.
He's really cute, he's really nice.
I met him, I found him and then,
like, you know, I think he gets along with Pi too.
Don't be worried for me.
I'm absolutely fine, healthy.
Go say hi to Danny.
I'll go over there.
I don't, I don't, I've had enough of
people talking about diseases and stuff.
Let's talk about healthy things, okay?
But I'll be back guys.
Love you, thank you.